[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[reporter] More than a thousand
guns, including rifles
and other firearms amounting
to over 50 million pesos,
are currently in police custody
after being seized
from a shipment made by Red Dragon.
[Raul] Why did you wear that mask?
[Diego] I'll do whatever it takes
to stop Red Dragon.
I'm telling you,
I didn't sabotage the shipment.
Then who did it?!
An impostor who goes around
and calls himself Jaguar.
[Lily] I have eyes watching you
even when I'm away.
So, don't you ever dare.
[Emilia] Mama, that's my husband, Raul.
-Well, what do you do?
-I run a small jewelry business.
I didn't know you had
a thing for peasants.
It's an anonymous text, Mom.
It says they have proof that
Helena Montoya is Red Dragon.
This could be a trap.
I'm sorry, Mom, but I'm willing
to take that risk.
And that's because I'm done
playing games with Red Dragon.
I've lost my patience.
[Damian] Raul couldn't have done it.
The last time I saw him,
he was shot in the stomach.
But the man on the CCTV footage
didn't look like he was injured.
Diego's pretending to be Jaguar.
[Diego] I'm taking you on your last ride!
You'll never be the governor
of this province while I'm alive.
[pensive music playing]
[exhales]
Damn it.
My mama burned you so bad.
What's with her anyway?
Is she really a philanthropist?
Why does she talk like that?
She's like a fire-breathing dragon!
[Natalie yelps]
-Who are you?!
-Madrigal!
[Natalie] Aren't you happy to see me?
I thought you liked me.
What do you want, really?
[Jepoy] Why did you save me from Jaguar?
I want you to work for me.
[Jepoy] What do you want me to do?
[Natalie] Can you make me happy?
I have what you need.
And you have exactly what I want.
-You're lucky I found you.
-I knew you'd save me.
[Jepoy] Be careful next time.
I don't want this happening again.
[Natalie] You have feelings for Madrigal.
Could he actually love me? How?
Through Lily.
I want to make a proposal.
I want to help Lily.
Lily Cruz refused my help? Is she insane?
Who exactly is stopping me from
joining forces with Lily Cruz?
-It's Anna.
-What?
I want you, Madrigal.
And I know that I'll have you.
Even if it means that I need
to swallow my pride…
and bow down to Lily Cruz.
I'll do it.
For you.
[birds chirping]
I'm fine, Emilia.
I am as strong as a horse.
Diego has always had it in for you.
And right now,
he's poisoning Arnaldo's mind.
So, why don't you do the same?
And look how that turned out?
The black sheep is still alive.
So, please.
Don't chastise an old man
who's got a bomb ticker.
Papa, Diego said he'd do
everything to prevent
your return to office.
Why am I telling you this?
Unlike Mama, all you ever do
is talk down on me.
But I still care for you no matter what.
So, in times like these,
we need to team up.
We will, Emilia.
But you do not tell me what to do.
If Diego dies, I want to make
sure it's my call,
and that I'll leave no trace.
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
[door opens]
See you later, Mom.
[tense music continues]
Lily? What's wrong?
[tense music swells]
What's the matter?
I feel like someone's watching us.
Watching our every move.
Let's go. Get in the car.
Stay safe, Mom. Please go inside.
All right. Be careful, you two.
We will.
[tense music continues]
[car door opens]
Why are you here watching over Lily?
Didn't I tell you to stop bothering us?
Don't you have anything else to do?
Weren't you listening to me the other day?
I told you, I was gonna offer
my help to Lily Cruz.
Are you, really?
What will you get from helping Lily Cruz?
Why don't you just stop bugging us?
Do you think it's that easy?
I didn't save your life for nothing!
I wasn't having sex with you
for no reason.
What kind of woman
do you think I am, huh?!
I wanted to help Lily because I'm hoping…
that… [sobs]
that you'd see something good in me.
[somber music playing]
I was hoping you would like me back.
[Natalie sobs]
Ma'am…
No.
It meant nothing, right?
What?
What did you say?
I should've known. Just leave my car.
Get out of my car, Madrigal.
-[whispers] Ma'am…
-I said, get out!
Get out! [sobs]
[sobs]
Just go!
[cries]
No!
[bawls]
No doubt the Ardientes will
try to have you killed again.
[birds chirping]
I'm not backing down.
And he will never get back in power again.
I just…
I wish I had prevented him
from cheating in the first place.
Diego, we did everything for you to win.
You did your part,
and so did the rest of us.
Don't ever regret doing the right thing
just because you didn't win.
I will keep fighting for you
and everyone else…
who suffers for justice like you do.
[romantic music playing]
And it's because of people like you…
that I find the courage to go on.
I've been wanting to give you this.
[romantic music continues]
This is for you.
It looks great on you.
Thanks for everything, Diego.
I love you so much.
Come on.
[bawling]
[suspenseful music playing]
Face it, Natalie.
[whimpers]
He doesn't love you.
He will never love you.
He will never love you!
No one will ever love you!
[bawls]
No one will love you, Natalie.
Can't you see?
[Natalie] Arnaldo.
He didn't love you.
Raul…
[Natalie] He just used you!
And he chose
Emilia.
And Madrigal?
[screams]
No!
I'm done sleeping with men…
who don't want to give me their love.
You… You even tried to coexist
with pathetic losers!
What were you thinking?
[suspenseful music swells]
I will come back.
And I will recuperate.
And when I do,
I'll come back with a vengeance!
WHERE ARE YOU?
Why do I keep thinking about you, Jepoy?
Why am I worried about you?
Shouldn't I be mad at you
for going with that woman?
I hate this!
Why am I even feeling this way?
Anna?
[romantic music playing]
Hey, hey, hey. Wait.
Let's talk-- Where are you going?
You're not going anywhere.
We need to talk.
Listen. You don't have to talk.
Just hear me out.
My deal with Natalie, about Lily?
It's all over. We're not going
to go through with it.
So? Are you happy now?
No.
What else do you want?
I did that for you, Anna.
Natalie won't bother Lily
anymore now that I called
the deal off with her. Problem solved.
What about you?
What if she tries to get you back?
[romantic music continues]
Do you know why I didn't
want you to make that deal?
Because I don't want to see you together.
Because, Jepoy…
I don't think I can take it.
What do you mean?
-[whimpers]
-Why not?
Ouch! What's wrong?
That hurts, Anna. Tell me. What's wrong?
Isn't it obvious?!
Jepoy, I like you.
[romantic music swells]
I like you.
Jepoy, I tried to deny
my feelings for you.
I tried turning my attention to Diego…
because I'd rather love someone else…
than see you keep your hopes up for Lily.
If you truly love Lily,
I'd accept that, Jepoy.
I'd be okay with it.
But you know what hurts?
It's to see you and Natalie together!
That's just not fair!
Because I've always been here
for you, Jepoy!
-Anna…
-I'm just here, waiting.
-Why her? Why, Jepoy?
-Don't cry. [shushes]
-Don't cry. It's okay.
-[cries]
Anna, there's nothing
between me and Natalie.
That's the truth.
I promise.
I'm sorry, Jepoy.
Maybe I just needed to let this all out.
I hope nothing changes between
us because of what I said.
-I'm really sorry.
-Anna, wait! Anna!
[Anna exhales, sniffles]
Anna.
What's wrong?
[Jepoy] Anna!
[Arnaldo] Jepoy.
What did you do to Anna?
Jepoy…
[Diego] Careful, okay?
I should've worn flats today, Diego.
[Ivy and Diego chuckle]
[dramatic music playing]
Wait here. I'll just go check on Arnaldo.
[dramatic music continues]
[tense music playing]
[phone chimes]
LET'S MEET AT
PACIFIC RESTAURANT NOW.
[Diego] Arnaldo's not there.
Maybe he went out with Anna.
The anonymous tipster texted me again.
Are you going?
In times like these, Diego,
I need to take risks…
so I can find the evidence I need.
Promise me you'll stay safe,
and make sure you meet in a public place.
If you want, I can come with you.
No, it's okay. I can handle this myself.
Let's go then.
-I'll help you back.
-Okay.
-Oh!
-Careful.
[eerie music]
I'm all right.
[tense music playing]
Watch your step.
Good evening, ma'am.
-Have you secured the area?
-Yes, ma'am.
The area is secured.
Thank you.
Where are they?
Over there.
Thank you.
[suspenseful music playing]
[laughing]
-You?
-Got you!
You're the one who texted me?
And you're the one investigating my mother
and desperately trying
to connect her to Red Dragon.
Emilia, that is not true.
Did you know Mama
threatened me just recently?
So I won't even dare cross her.
Now, I'm here tonight, Emilia,
because I want to catch
the culprit myself.
That's all it is.
Yeah, right, Lily.
I have evidence against you.
Well, that evidence is useless, then.
Do you want to know why?
Because Mama will believe me.
[chuckles] That's what you think.
Remember, I am her daughter.
I am the daughter your mom wishes she had.
You see, when Mama and I are together,
time seems to fly by so fast
because we talk about so many things.
And your name hardly comes up
in the conversation
because she is so disappointed in you.
No wonder she wishes
I was her daughter instead.
-That is not true.
-Yes, it is.
Well, Emilia?
I bet you wish I just died
inside that flimsy coffin, huh?
I bet you wished
you never left a phone in there
and that you actually succeeded
at killing me
because otherwise, I wouldn't be here now.
Well, I'm sorry.
Wishes are all you've got now
because I'm here in front
of you, alive and kicking.
Do you really think, Emilia,
that I've forgotten everything
you've done to me?
No, Emilia, I haven't forgotten at all!
Then again, I'm not in a rush
because I still have to sort out
my plans for you.
Option one: I can throw you in jail,
but that would be too boring.
Do you want to know
what my second option is?
To bury you alive in a ditch
that you'll be digging out yourself.
And I assure you, Emilia,
not even Satan will be able to save you.
[tense music intensifies]
So, you'd best not get on my bad side
because I won't think twice
about burying you alive.
Stop it, Lily.
Mama might get to you first.
[laughs]
Mama would do that? Why?
Does she spit out fire when she gets mad?
[suspenseful music playing]
Hey. What's the matter?
Why can't you answer me?
Tell me, Emilia! Come on. Am I right?
Does she spit fire when she's angry?
Spill the beans, Emilia. Come on.
You just shut up and leave
my mother alone!
I'll try. I'll try my best.
But the thing is, sometimes,
there's just no stopping me.
[tense music playing]
[exhales]
[suspenseful music playing]
Anna, Jepoy.
You look a little happier
than usual, Arnaldo.
Well… I think I saw an angel.
You know, Diego's friend.
The one he was with earlier.
I just want to ask… Is she his girlfriend?
-[Anna] What?
-Is she my brother's girlfriend?
[Anna] Um…
[stutters] No.
[quietly] She's not?
[Anna] But… I know they're getting there.
[unsettling music]
She's our friend, Lily.
[dramatic music]
Lily.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
If she's your friend,
can you introduce me to her?
[tense music continues]
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" playing]
Thanks for everything, Diego.
[song continues]
[Diego] It's a bit cheesy, but I hope
you feel me holding you
when you wear that.
Wear it close to your heart
as a token of my undying love.
[song fades]
[tense piano music playing]
[tense music swells]
[Julio] Arnaldo.
Who are you?
Well, if you want to quit politics,
what do you want to do?
-I want to be a priest.
-[chokes]
No matter what you say,
I'm not going with you!
I was led here to fulfill
a mission. I can't just leave.
[henchman] I'm sorry, ma'am,
but they ganged up on us.
We weren't able to take
Diego Torillo with us.
[tense music continues]
[Julio] Damn you, Diego Torillo!
What did you do to my grandson?!
[Lily] I tried looking for it,
Diego. I really did.
But I couldn't find it. I'm so sorry.
It's okay. It's just a necklace.
Better that than me losing you.
-It's not just a necklace.
-[chuckles softly]
Everything you gave and did for me, Diego…
They're all important to me.
I don't want you to think
I'm taking all that for granted.
They're all important to me.
[romantic music playing]
Lily, you don't have to prove anything.
I know I'm important to you.
And even if this fight goes on forever,
I'll still be happy as long
as you're by my side.
Don't worry about it.
Come on. It's just a necklace.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I'll just buy a new one.
Okay?
[whispering] Anna, this is dangerous.
[tense music playing]
Lily shouldn't have come here.
But he didn't recognize her, right?
Yeah, for now.
Arnaldo was crazy obsessed
with Ivy back then.
What if his memories
come back because of her?
Jepoy, let's just do what Lily said.
For now, let's take care of Arnaldo.
What if the old Arnaldo comes back?
The heartless bastard…
who killed Nanny Carlotta.
Are we still going to protect him then?
If that does happen, Jepoy,
are you actually going to kill him?
Yes. Without a doubt.
The question is…
if Arnaldo returns to being
the devil we once knew,
will you still protect him?
[tense music playing]
I hope you've really changed, Arnaldo.
Because if you haven't and you
try to hurt the ones I love,
then you'll be dealing with me.
[tense music swells]
Everyone can change.
Even the ones who made your life hell.
I really hope I wasn't wrong
about you, Arnaldo.
Aren't you going to sleep yet?
Later. You go ahead and rest.
All right. I'll go on in.
Jepoy, isn't that Lily?
Where's Arnaldo?
He's asleep.
All right. Let's go meet Lily.
[Lily] Jepoy, Anna.
-[Anna] Lily, why are you here?
-Jepoy--
I need your help.
I need you to do something for me.
[Diego] Lily, you have to be careful.
We're up against
some very powerful people.
What if they catch you?
That won't happen, because I will reveal
that Helena Montoya and
Red Dragon are one and the same.
How are you going to do that?
How will you get past her lackeys?
I asked Jepoy for help.
I sent him out to do something.
I planned it out.
Just be careful.
[tense music playing]
[doctor] It's 120/80.
-Your blood pressure is normal.
-[Julio scoffs]
Just continue taking your medicine
and getting plenty of rest,
and you'll be back to your old self.
Doc, I've already told you
that my condition
will only get worse
as long as my grandson
stays the way he is now.
What I need you to do
is to bring back Arnaldo.
I mean, bring my grandson
back to how he was.
The Arnaldo I know. Not this…
Not this goody-two-shoes wannabe
who gives me a migraine.
There are alternative
treatments, Governor.
Unconventional, but effective
in some cases.
We can use hypnosis,
or maybe acupuncture to treat the patient.
How can you do that when
my grandson isn't even here?
Sometimes, you just need to
jump-start the patient's brain.
By that, I mean images that'll
ignite an intense emotion.
[Jepoy] Thanks.
Lily.
I've done what you asked me to.
This is a clone of Mercedes' phone.
You can keep track of all her calls
and text messages from here.
Thank you, Jepoy.
I can always count on you.
-[Pandoy] One for you.
-[Loring] Hmm.
-There.
-Here we go.
-One for Diego. One for me.
-[Loring chuckles]
-Nanny, Uncle.
-[Loring] Come and join us.
-Diego, you're just in time.
-That looks really good!
Of course. I prepared
all of your favorites.
-[Pandoy] Right.
-Yummy, right?
It's not my birthday we're celebrating.
[Pandoy] Hey.
She's been thinking of what
to prepare since last week.
-[Loring] That's true.
-[Pandoy chuckles]
This is why I love you so much, Nanny.
-[Diego] Besides, Uncle…
-Yes?
Our birthday only comes once a year,
so we have to celebrate.
Well, I hope Lily can come
to my birthday tomorrow.
That reminds me, where's Lily?
Has she found Red Dragon?
That's what she's doing right now.
She cloned the phone
of Red Dragon's secretary
to keep tabs on everything they do.
You can do that?
How?
-Cloning…
-Oh, whatever.
At least we know Lily's doing something.
-Right. Let's just eat.
-Yes. This is what's important.
-You have to try this.
-That's right.
-I made your favorites.
-Looks like I'm gonna eat a lot, Nanny.
-Yes!
-I know.
[tense music playing]
[ringing]
[Mercedes] Madam?
I've already settled my problem
with Mr. Yi…
…regarding the gun shipment.
What about the guns
in the possession of the police?
I've already dealt with that.
[Red Dragon] They won't be able
to trace them to me.
[Mercedes] I have one other
concern, Madam.
Emilia says she wants
to get rid of someone.
[Red Dragon] Prioritize the shipment.
And I will take care of my daughter.
Yes.
[tense music swells]
It's confirmed.
That's another piece of evidence proving
that Helena Montoya is Red Dragon.
But with all of the supposed
good things she has done,
the people of Poblacion Ardiente
now see her as an angel.
Let's see if they'll still
see her as an angel
once I expose all of her crimes.
I'll gather more evidence to
prove to the people of Ardiente
just who the real Helena Montoya is.
The people of Poblacion Ardiente
will soon learn
that their supposed angel
is actually a devil in disguise.
"And he was so surprised to see the turtle
standing on the top of the mountain
because he knew he had lost the race.
All the rabbit could do was cry."
Well, kids? Did you like our story today?
We did!
All right, we'll finish the rest
of the stories tomorrow.
You have to go home now.
It's getting late.
[kid 1] Teacher Anna, Teacher Anna,
can you go with us?
Of course. I can walk with you
to the entrance. Shall we go?
-[children] Yes, ma'am!
-Okay.
[Anna] Come on. Let's go.
Careful.
You go with them, Anna.
I'll clean up here.
Jepoy.
Go on. I won't do anything to him.
Remember what I told you.
[Anna] Let's go.
There. [chuckles]
[tense music playing]
Here. One, two, three.
[Jepoy] What if the old Arnaldo
comes back?
Are you actually going to kill him?
Without a doubt.
Wow.
My friend fish swim pretty fast.
[suspenseful music playing]
[door opens]
[Julio] Every corner of Poblacion Ardiente
is etched in my mind.
But it's not the same for you,
that's why you have to study this.
Until you can control every piece of it
from wherever you are.
That is the mark of a true leader.
Arnaldo, you are the man.
Who else would I take after?
I learned from the best.
-Cheers!
-[Julio] To Mayor Arnaldo!
-[Arnaldo] Like you said.
[Arnaldo] Failure is not an option.
[Julio] You'll be running
for senator in my place.
[Julio] You need Miss Aguas
for your candidacy.
[doctor] Sometimes, you
just need to jump start
the patient's brain.
By that, I mean images that'll
ignite an intense emotion.
[tense music continues]
[Julio] I'm sure Ivy can sponsor
this event for you.
If it's okay,
I'd rather leave Ivy out of this.
I don't want her to think
that we're only after her money
or that we're just using her.
But it's the truth, right?
Actually, no. Not anymore.
I'm already in love with her.
[Julio] What's going on with you?
You're so obsessed with Miss Aguas.
-[Julio] You can't even think…
-[Lily] You monster!
-…straight anymore.
-[Arnaldo] I didn't mean to!
You bastard!
Arnaldo, get up!
[Arnaldo] Don't touch me!
Stay out of this!
[Julio] Arnaldo. You were the
golden boy of our family.
How could you let that woman
ruin your life?!
I! V! Y!
-[Julio] Damn you, Ivy Aguas!
-[Arnaldo shouting]
[Julio] What have you done to my grandson?
I'm not done with you, Ivy.
I am not yet done with you!
[tense music swells]
I'll get you back, Arnaldo.
You'll be the man you once were.
I promise you that.
[suspenseful music playing]
Gee, you're fast!
But just you wait! I'll catch you!
There!
Man, this is hard.
Can't you guys just stay still?
[suspenseful music continues]
Hang on, Arnaldo,
you're not doing it right.
What am I doing wrong?
That's not how you catch catfish.
-[Jepoy] See?
-Where is it? Can I see?
[laughs]
You're all talk.
You didn't even catch one.
Fine. Your turn. Go on.
Let's see now. There. Hold on.
[suspenseful music swells]
Jepoy!
Anna, look. I caught one.
-[Jepoy] You did it. Nice!
-[Arnaldo and Jepoy chuckle]
[Arnaldo] So that's the trick!
Jepoy taught me how to catch catfish.
This one's huge!
-Pretty easy, right?
-Yeah. I get it now.
From now on, I'll do it
the way you taught me.
We sure caught a big one,
just enough for our dinner.
Do you know how to cook it?
The problem is that I still have to
gather firewood before cooking.
I'm not good at cooking,
but I'll figure it out soon.
I'm sure you'll get the hang of it.
[Arnaldo] Perfect. We caught three.
It goes really well with…
Arnaldo.
[tense music playing]
[Helena] You know,
when your phone blacks out,
it means it's been cloned.
-That's impossible, Madam.
-Shut up!
[Lily] I'm sure Red Dragon already knows
that I'm her enemy.
[Arnaldo] I've been having
some thoughts lately.
About a woman.
-[Diego] Well, what do you see?
-[Arnaldo] Uncontrollable lust.
[Diego] Don't you dare come
near my brother again.
I want you to kill Diego Torillo now!
[Helena] I just realized
that I'm allergic to flowers.
Lilies in particular.
[Emilia] I will watch how the queen works.
[Helena] Exactly.
[theme music playing]